travelonly.com 2004-06-10

# Travel Only - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Respecting your privacy is important to us. Any customer information you provide remains confidential at all times. We do not sell, rent or disclose any information about our customers to other companies except for third-party audits. Periodically, we will send product and service information that we feel would interest you by telephone, fax, e-mail or mail. If, however, you prefer to not receive such offers or information, please let us know by calling 1 (800) 608 1117 or by sending an e-mail to headoffice@travelonly.net.

Cookies   
A cookie is a piece of data – typically encoded information about how and when you use a site – that a Web server creates when you visit a Web site. This data is placed on your computer hard drive in the form of a small text file.   
There are two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used only for the length of time you stay on the Web site. When you leave the site, they expire and are no longer active. Persistent cookies are more permanent and can be re-read when you return to the site that placed them on your computer.

The Travel Only Web site uses session cookies to enable us to better serve you. You must enable cookies for this section of the Web site to function correctly. Travel Only does not use cookies to track any personal information about you, nor to collect any marketing data.

We do not and will not use cookies to retrieve data from your hard drive or to obtain your e-mail address or other personal information. 

You may choose not to accept cookies by setting your browser options to inform you when cookies are being sent. Alternately, you can set these options to deny cookies altogether. Please note, however, that by not accepting cookies you may limit the functionality that we can provide to you when you visit our site. 

To change your browser settings: 

Microsoft Internet Explorer 4: Select Options from the Internet Options. Select the Advanced menu and scroll to the Cookies section. You will have several options - accept cookies, ask permission before accepting cookies or disallow cookies. 

Microsoft Internet Explorer 5: Select Tools from your browser menu. Select Internet Options, Security, then Internet from the Web Content Zone, then select Custom Level. From the drop-down list, scroll down to Cookies and select the options you want. 

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6: On the Tools menu, click Internet Options, and then click the Privacy tab. Under Settings, move the slider to the privacy level you want. 

Netscape Communicator or Navigator: Select Preferences from the Edit menu. From the Preferences menu, select Advanced, and several cookie options will be listed in the lower right of the menu. There will be options that allow you to accept cookies, request permission before accepting or disallow cookies completely. 

Automatic Logging of Session Data   
To help us serve you better, we continuously and automatically collect generic, non-personal information about visits to our Web site. The following points describe the nature of the information collected in our Web server logs:   
We do not collect personal information such as names, ages, phone numbers, addresses or e-mail addresses from visitors to our Web site. We do not collect individual profile information for visitors across multiple sites and do not aggregate information from any other sources about browsing patterns of individual visitors across multiple sites.

We collect anonymous visitor information like IP addresses, browser types (such as Internet Explorer or Netscape), return visits from past guests, referring pages, pages visited along with the order in which they were visited, time spent on the Web site, and the referrer and transaction information for e-commerce pages. We collect such non-personally identifiable information for the following purposes: (1) to obtain anonymous statistical analysis of Web page traffic patterns for our Web site (2) to administer our Web site and servers, (3) to allow for auditing of our services by third parties, and (4) to improve our services.

As mentioned above, we use cookies only for more accurate anonymous traffic analysis As we do not build a database of individual visitors, the data that we do collect is never stored in any individual user profile; the data collected serves only to update aggregate counts allowing us to monitor traffic on our Web site.

We make use of customized JavaScript tracking code to track anonymous information about visitors' activity. This code contacts our suppliers’ servers, receives a cookie in response, and loads an image to the page. This 1 x 1 image is called a clear gif or Web bug. This JavaScript tracking code does not collect personal information such as name, age, phone number, mailing address or credit card numbers from visitors to our Web site. Visitors may elect to opt out of receiving tracking cookies used to collect information for our Web server logs. Note: the opt out option requires one cookie to function.

We do not create individual profiles of visitors. We do not have a database of individual profiles of each visitor. We collect data in aggregate form and data is not recorded or stored about individual visitors.

We may use the aggregate data to inform third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their Web sites.   
Travel Only reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.
